<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Untitled RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Untitled RSS Feed]]></description><link>https://mkhymohamed.github.io</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 07:33:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mkhymohamed.github.io/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Hello Github World!]]></title><description><![CDATA[<div id="preamble">
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="literalblock">
<div class="content">
<pre>:published_at: 2017-07-14</pre>
</div>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>"Hello world" is the first program that everyone wanted to code must code it. But in this article I do not mean going to code, here I want to introduce you some info about me and why coding.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>My passion for building things began when I was seven years, I started with playing games like FIFI2002 and what comes next FIFA2004, FIFA2006, FIFA2007, Euro2008, FIFA2009 that was the latest fifa series games I ever played so far.. I remember all details and memories So I became passionate with computer So since three years when I succeeded in high school, I made a decision to study computer science in the   college.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="sect1">
<h2 id="_why_blogs">Why blogs?</h2>
<div class="sectionbody">
<div class="paragraph">
<p>After reading more about CS and this field I think that to become <strong>software engineer</strong> you must be <strong>documented</strong>. So as they say is history to be record for your knowledge and development and that’s why I’ve decided to start recording my thoughts here and that’s why we document on Github and that’s why I say Hello Github World!.</p>
</div>
<div class="paragraph">
<p>In the long term, I want this blog to be a written record of my experience as <strong>a budding software engineer</strong> and <strong>human</strong>.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>]]></description><link>https://mkhymohamed.github.io/2017/07/14/Hello-Github-World.html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://mkhymohamed.github.io/2017/07/14/Hello-Github-World.html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mohamed Khaled Yousef]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>